(フリド)お前が ソラか…。
会いたかったぞ。
So you're Sora, huh?
I missed you.
Who're you?!
(ソラ)誰だ？
Hurry up...
Get over here... Sora!
(フリド)早く こっちに来い。 ソラ。
Who are you already?!
How do you know my name?
だから 誰なんだよ！
どうして オレの名を…。
Over here, come on!
こっちだ 早く。
チッ… 何を企んでやがる。
What's he planning?
Once I fly,
habataitara
I won't be coming back, I said.
modorena ito itte
And I set out.
mezashita no wa
For that blue, blue sky.
aoi aoi ano sora
I haven't learned "sadness" yet.
kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And I'm just starting to grasp "misery".
setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even this feeling I hold towards you.
anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
Is now turning into "words".
ima kotoba ni wakatteku
Waking up from the dream of this unknown world.
michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
I spread these wings and fly.
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
Once I fly,
habataitara
I won't be coming back, I said.
modorena ito itte
And I set out.
mezashita no wa
For that blue, blue sky.
aoi aoi ano sora
Knowing I'll find the answer,
tsuki nuketara
If I pierce through it.
mitsukaru to shitte
if I break free,
furikiru hodo
From that blue, blue sky.
aoi aoi ano sora
Contact
テメエ いったい 何を…。
What the hell are you up to?
なんだ？ このにおい…。
What's that smell?
(フリド)ハッハッハッハッ…。
I'll let you have one, too!
お前にも やるよ。
ウワッ！ アチチ… アチッ…！
Whoa, hot-hot...?
(ソラ)焼き芋？
(フリド)ハハハハッ…。
A baked sweet potato?
(フリド)ハハハハ。
(フリド)待ちくたびれたぞ。
I was getting tired of waiting for you.
あまりにも退屈なんで
芋 焼いて待ってたんだよ。
And I got so bored I baked
some sweet potatoes while I waited.
ハフ… おっ！
結構いけるぞ これ。
Oh! This is pretty good!
ソラ。 お前も こっち来て食えよ。
Sora!
Come on over here!
(ソラ)オレを待ってたって言ったよな。
You said you were waiting for me, right?
減ってんだろ？ 腹。
You're hungry, aren't you?
(フリド)うん うめぇ！
This is good!
うめぇな！
I told you!
Have some more.
だろう！ もっと食え。
におうな…。
Something smells...
That's because you're eating
a sweet potato.
そりゃ 芋 食ってるからな。
アハハハハ！
(ソラ)風が吹き抜けるとき
運んでくるんだよ。
The smell is carried on the wind
as it blows through...
キタネ様の隠し墓の土のにおいをな。
The smell of the earth from
Kitane-sama's hidden tomb...
この バチかぶり野郎が！
Blasphemous!
ハッ！
コイツ…。
This jerk...
出されたもん
黙って食べんかい！
Just shut up and eat
what you've been served!
そっちも！
４人のご遺体を返しやがれ！
The same goes for you!
Give back the four bodies.
さもなきゃ… バチ 当てるぞ！
If you don't...
you'll receive divine retribution!
ハハハハハ！
(フリド)バチなんざ 生まれてこのかた
当たりっぱなしよ。
I've been receiving divine retribution
ever since I was born.
だが 不思議と
死なんもんでな。 お前も➡
But the funny thing is
I just don't seem to die.
You should do whatever you want...
やりたいようにやらにゃあ…
人にバチなんか当ててる場合かよ。
It's not the time for you to be
giving people retribution.
フッ… あぁ やりたいように
やらせてもらうぜ。
That's right...
I will  do what I want.
だから テメエを… ぶっ倒す!!
So I'm going to beat you!
オラァ!!
うっ…。
なめやがって！
Don't mess with me!
ほら どうした！
Oh, what's the matter?!
《ソラ : コイツ… なんなんだ？》
Who the hell... is this guy?
(フウカ)あら… もう 終わり？
Oh, are you done already?
(フウカ)ちょっと
やりすぎちゃったかしら？
I might've gone a little overboard...
でも…。
But...
(フウカ)おこげを払えば 大丈夫。
It'll be okay if I remove
the scorched part.
You're mine!
(ナルト)もらった!!
Wind Style:
Scattering Flower Dance!
風遁 花散舞！
She can use... Wind Style...
風遁って コイツ…。
Earth, fire, water, lightning
and wind...
土 火 水 雷 風…
すべての属性の術を使えるのか。
She can use Jutsu from
all the Chakra natures?
フフフフフ… びっくりした？
Are you surprised?
There are still many things
you don't know, boy...
まだまだ 坊やには知らないことが
多いのよ 女にはね！
About women, I mean.
Don't run away.
逃げちゃ ダメよ。
I'm going to tell you about
the mysteries of my female body.
このフウカ様の女体の神秘
教えてあげるんだから。
Yikes. There's a mystery
I don't want to know about...
冗談じゃねえ…。 そんな神秘
知りたくねえっつうんだよ！
Fire Style: Phoenix Flower Jutsu!
火遁 鳳仙火の術！
Water Style: Mouth of the Serpent.
水遁 邪の口！
うわっ！
Damn it. What's going on?
クソ！ どうなってんだ!?
Uh oh!
やべぇ！
雷遁 地走り！
Lightning Style: Earth Flash!
What's the matter, huh?!
(フリド)どうした？ あぁ!?
もう 終わりか？
Are you done already?
チクショウ!!
Damn it!
You've got spirit!
いいガッツだ！
Now I think it's about time
you showed me your true power!
それじゃ そろそろ
見せてもらおうかな。
お前の本当の力を！
And do it without using
a toy like this!
こんなおもちゃ 使ってねえでよ。
(フリド)ケッ！ ダメか…。
No good, huh?
Hold it...
(ソラ)待ちやがれ…。
《な… なんだ？ これ。
What is this?
Oh, but this sensation...
いや でも この感じ…》
If you want to see my power
that badly...
そんなに オレの力が見てえなら
とくと 拝みやがれ！
Take a good look!
Yes! Yes!
そうだろう そうだろう！
《フリド : だが まだ完全ではない…》
But... it's still not complete...
やっと やる気が
出てきたみてえだな。
It looks like you've finally
gotten motivated!
Do your chattering in hell!
地獄で ほざきやがれ！
That's a fine wind!
いい風だ！
Beast Wave: Palm Hurricane!
(ソラ)獣波烈風掌!!
(サクラ)早く みんなと合流しないと。
We've got to join up
with the others quick...
ナルトとソラが心配だわ！
I'm worried about Naruto and Sora...
サイ…!? サイ！
Sai?!
Sai!
(サイ)ちょっと
フラっとしただけです。
I just got a little lightheaded.
早く ナルトたちを見つけましょう。
Let's find Naruto and
the others quickly.
《思ったより
毒のまわりが早かったのね…》
The poison spread faster
than I thought...
どうですか？ たまに
弱味を見せてあげると➡
What do you think?
If you show weakness
once in a while,
人との距離は ぐっと縮まると…。
you can get closer to people...
本に書いてあったなんて
言ったら 許さないわよ！
I won't allow it if you say
that was written in a book.
(サクラ)大切なことはね…➡
You don't find the most important
things in books!
本なんかに書いてやしない。
こうやって
体で覚えてくしかないんだから。
You just have to physically
learn things like that.
そうですね…。
You're right.
《ヤマト : みんなは どこに…》
Where is everyone?
だったら… 影分身の術！
Then I'll use this Shadow Clone Jutsu!
チッ…！
おっ 風が… よ～し！
Oh, the wind stopped! All right.
…ん？
Whoa, what's this?!
わ～っ なんじゃこりゃ!?
よくも…➡
How dare you...
よくも私を殺してくれたね。
How dare you kill me!
Huh?! What?!
Is it a Substitution?
えっ… なに？ 変わり身!?
You're the bane of women, boy.
女泣かせの坊やだねぇ。
この長さにするまで
何年かかると思ってるの？
Do you have any idea how many years
it took to grow my hair this long?
髪は女の命…。
Hair is the most important thing
to a woman...
You will take responsibility
その命を傷つけた責任は
とってもらうわよ！
for damaging my most
important feature!
《体が動かねえ… 金縛りの術!?》
I can't move.
Is this a Paralysis Jutsu?
Damn it!
クソッ… いつの間に!?
Just like that...
Now boy, let's share a hot kiss.
さあ 坊や
熱いキス かわしましょう。
(フウカ)ただし 魂はいただくわよ。
But your soul will be mine.
く… くるな！
S-Stay away!
さあ…！
Now...
イテエ…！
クソッ！ ヤツは どこ行きやがった!?
Damn it!
Where'd he go?
What?!
What the hell happened here?
何だ？ いったい何があったんだ!?
(フリド)お前の力だ。
It's your power!
You altered the landscape
オレの術を弾き返そうとして
繰り出した➡
with the power you unleashed
in an attempt to repel my Jutsu.
お前の力が 景色を変えた。
これが お前の本当の力だ。
This is your true power...
これが… オレの本当の力…。
This is... my true power...
That's right.
Heaven granted you that power.
(フリド)そうだ その力は
お前が 天から授かったもんだ。
It's still got a long way to go.
まだまだ こんなもんじゃねえ。
It will become a much
more massive power.
もっと どでかい力となる。
あんな ちっぽけな寺に➡
So much so that you won't be able
to remain suppressed
in that tiny little temple...
くすぶってなんか
いられないぐらいな。
That's why you must seriously
consider how you use that power.
だからこそ お前
その力の使いみちを➡
真剣に考えなくちゃ
いけねえぞ。
ハンッ 訳わかんねえこと
言ってんじゃねえよ。
Cut out the gibberish.
Will you use it for your own gain
or as outbursts of your emotion?
(フリド)己の欲得
感情の発露に使うか➡
Or will you go beyond your home
and village and
それとも 己の家 里を越え➡
offer up that power for this nation,
the Land of Fire?
この国
火ノ国のために捧げるか。
…なるほど オレは
バチ当たりかもしれない。
I see. I might very well be
a terrible guy.
But in life those four people
in the hidden tombs
だが 隠し墓の あの４人はな
生前 火ノ国を思い➡
fought and died for the Land of Fire.
戦い 死んだ。
オレが その遺体を➡
If I were to say I was going to
use the bodies for the Land of Fire...
火ノ国のために
使おうというのであれば➡
I wonder if they would nail me
with divine retribution.
果たして ヤツら
オレ様に バチなんざ当てるかな？
火ノ国のために？
For the Land of Fire...
That's right! I will use this power
for the Land of Fire.
そうだ オレは火ノ国のために
この力を使う！
Who the hell are you?
テメエ… いったい何者なんだ？
…赤子のお前を
オレは 抱いたことがある。
I've once held you as a baby.
I know... your father...
お前の父親を…
オレは 知っている。
…なんだって!?
What did you say?
フフフ…。
Reaper Kiss.
屍鬼接吻。
《なんだ!?
What? My Chakra...
チャクラが…》
What is this place?
ここは!?
むっ。
うん？
N-Naruto!
ナルト!! アンタ 何やってんのよ!!
Y-You! What're you doing?!
No, something's wrong...
いや… 何か 様子がおかしい。
親父を 知ってるだと？
You say... you know my dad?
うわ～!!
Naruto?!
ナルト！ うわ～!!
うぅ!! ナルト!!
Naruto!
Let Naruto go!
ナルトを 離せ！
あぁっ!!
Are you okay, Sakura?
大丈夫か サクラ？
Captain Yamato.
ヤマト隊長！
ふん！
I won't let you interfere!
ジャマは させないよ！
(フドウ)土遁 岩柱牢の術！
Earth Style:
Stone Pillar Prison Jutsu!
あっ！
しまった！
Oh no!
フフフ…！
《はっ！ な なんなの!?
この邪悪なチャクラは！》
What?!
What is this evil Chakra?!
キャー!!
Fouka?!
フウカ…。
ゲホッ ゲホッ!!
アイタタ…。
Damn you.
クソー テメエ！
You jerks!
I'll give all of you
posthumous names!
テメエら まとめて戒名つけてやる！
ソラ！
Sora...
-Huh?!
-What?
なに!?
あら この子…。
Oh, this is the kid...
Oh, he's the one, huh?
へぇ… コイツが。
(ソラ)加勢に来たぞ。
I've come to back you up!
誰も頼んでねえってばよ！
Nobody asked for that!
You're the one who called for help!
お前が助けを呼んだんじゃねえか。
I didn't call for help
or anything like that.
オレは 助けなんか
呼んじゃいねえぞ！
I see...
そうか。 でも
来ちまったもんはしようがねえ。
But as long as I'm here,
I have no choice...
Let's go!
いくぞ！
おう！
Right!
Naruto! Sora! It's dangerous to fight!
Get out of there!
ナルト ソラ 戦うのは危険だ！
(ヤマト)逃げろ！
そうはさせない！
I don't think so!
It appears we'll just have to do this.
やるしかなさそうだな。
ヘッ ３対２かよ。
It's three against two.
It's four against one because
you'll just get in the way.
テメエが足引っ張るから４対１だよ。
チッ。
Naruto!
ナルト！
What is it?
何だ？
知るか！
Hell if I know!
I'm sorry we're late!
(地陸)遅れてすまぬ！
Assistance is here!
助太刀参上！
Chiriku-san...
(ヤマト)地陸さん！
(ソラ)地陸様！
Chiriku-sama!
Now what will you do?!
さぁ どうする？
(フエン)ぼちぼち いいんじゃない？
Isn't it about time?
You're right. It doesn't look like
we need to stall for time.
そうね
時間稼ぎは必要なさそうね。
Who the hell is he?
アイツはいったい…。
To the Hidden Leaf?
(ソラ)オレが木ノ葉に？
うむ。
Yes.
We have to go back to
the Village Hidden in the Leaves for a bit.
(ヤマト)ボクたちは
いったん木ノ葉の里に➡
戻らなくてはなりません。
Now that things have
turned out this way,
ことが こうなった以上➡
we need to once again solicit
instruction from the Hokage-sama.
改めて火影様の
指示を仰ぐ必要があります。
And our team will probably continue
to be in charge of this incident.
(ヤマト)引き続き この事件は➡
ボクたちの班が
担当することになるでしょう。
How about it, Sora?
Could you help us out?
どうだろう ソラ君 ボクたちに
力を貸してはもらえないかな？
Unfortunately, as you can see,
あいにくと サイがご覧のとおりで➡
it will take time for Sai to recover.
復帰には時間がかかる。
隠し墓を守ってきた
火ノ寺のキミなら➡
Since you're from the Fire Temple
and have been protecting
the hidden tombs,
I think you would more than
adequately fill the gap left by Sai.
サイの抜けた穴を十分に
埋めてくれると思うんだけどな。
We don't need to force ourselves
to ask him to come, do we?
別に無理に
誘わなくてもいいんじゃねえの？
Naruto!
ナルト！
(サクラ)アンタ少しは➡
For once can't you think
about where you are?!
場所をわきまえなさいよ！
ホント バチ当たるわよ！
You really will receive divine retribution.
(地陸)外の世界を見るのも➡
Seeing the outside world might
also be good training for you.
お前にとっては
いい修行になると思うが。
Either way, you're the one
who must decide, Sora.
いずれにせよ
決めるのはお前だ ソラ。
《ヤツらの罠…。
They weren't targeting Chiriku
with their traps.
あれは 地陸さんを
狙ったものではなかった。
Then we can presume that...
ならば 考えられるのは…》
I look up at the rainbow I saw as a child.
kodomo no koro mita niji wo
But the prism colors are gone,
ima miageru to nanairo de wa naku
Shrouded in mist instead.
yagate kiri ga kakari
I search for you as you change,
jikan wa sugi kawatte yuku
With the passage of time but you're nowhere to be found.
kimi wo sagashite mo doko ni mo inai
I close my eyes and open my heart.
me wo toji kokoro hiraite
And stare hard again just to see if nothing really changes.
mata nagemete mite mo nani mo kawaranai no ka
I need to know.
tashikamete mitai
I make a wish that the mist will clear.
sunao ni narereba kono kiri ga hareru to
If I'm true to myself and shout it out.
kokoro ni negai sou sakenderu
Maybe by losing something.
nanika wo nakushite shimatta koto de sou
There must be something I gain as well.
te ni shita mono mo kitto arun darou
But we're still confused about adulthood.
dakedo mada bokura wa otona ni tomadoi
(サイ)へぇ～ ナルトが使う螺旋丸て➡
四代目火影様がつくった術なんだ。
And searching for the means to live on.
ikito yuku sube sagashiteru
あぁ！ しかも会得難易度
Ａランクの超高等忍術なんだぜ。
そんなにすごい
術だなんて 知らなかったなぁ。
Next Episode
あの術はさぁ
エロ仙人に教わったんだってばよ！
Okay, I have to write up a report,
so I'm out of here.
地味だけど すげえキツイ修業でさぁ。
And I have to take Sai to the hospital.
最初にやったのが チャクラで➡
-Let's go, Sai.
-Right.
Huh? Wait a minute.
I need to continue my training...
水風船の水を
回転させて割る 回転の修業。
Kakashi Sensei isn't back yet, right?
You show Sora around the Leaf.
その次が 風船を
ゴムボールに替えての 威力の修業。
I refuse. Who'd want to hang around
with this  guy?
これが なかなか割れねえんだ。
んでもって最後が チャクラの回転を➡
Don't complain.
We're counting on you, Naruto.
手の中に留める 圧縮の修業。
Sora's now our teammate
on Team Kakashi, so...
すんげえ 難しかったんだけど➡
Teammate
Next time: "Teammate"
影分身を
利用する方法を思いついて➡
みごと 螺旋丸を
完成させたんだってばよ！
No kidding?
So the Rasengan you use
is a jutsu created by the Fourth Hokage Lord.
すごいなぁ さすが…。
まぁ それほどでもあるってばよ！
Yeah. And it's a super advanced ninjutsu
with an A-rank learning difficulty level.
ナハッ ハハッ…。
やだなぁ もう！ 言いすぎ
だってばよ サイそれはさ アハハハッ…。
I never knew it was such an amazing jutsu.
I learned it from the Pervy Sage.
He taught it to me with some unexciting,
but incredibly tough training.
First I did “rotation” training
where I used chakra to rotate water
in a water balloon until it popped.
And next I did “strength” training
where I switched from a balloon
to a rubber ball.
It's really difficult to break.
And finally I did “compression” training
where I built up the rotation
of chakra in my hand.
It was really difficult,
but I hit upon the approach
of using a Shadow Clone
and skillfully completed the Rasengan!
That's amazing. I gotta hand it to you.
Well, it's not that big of a deal.
Really! You're embarrassing me, Sail
"ULTIMATE HOW TO: MAKE YOUR FRIENDS FEEL BETTER"